Guide to the Harry H. Love papers, 1907-1964.
Love, Harry H. papers, 1907-1964.
- Kayes, Dr. H. K. 1930-1943 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Hill, E. B. Rio Piedras, P. R. 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Group Hospital Service, Inc. 1945 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- House- Correspondence re. rental, etc. 1930-1931 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Humbert, E. P. 1913-1934 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Income Tax- State and Federal 1918-1947 (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Insurance 1909-1914 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Insurance 1915-1930 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Insurance 1931-1944 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Insurance N. D. (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Ithaca High School Baseball Team 1922-1930 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Ithaca Journal-News, Ithaca, N. Y. (Box 7, Folder 78)
- Correspondence J 1948-& N. D. (Box 7, Folder 79)
- Keim, F. D. 1924-1950 (Box 7, Folder 80)
- Knudsen, Dr. L. 1918-1920 (Box 7, Folder 81)
- Correspondence -L 1949 (Box 7, Folder 82)
- Ladd, Dean C. E. College of Agriculture. 1939-1942 (Box 7, Folder 83)
- Land Grant College Association. 1922-1944 (Box 7, Folder 84)
- Langham, D. G. Venezuela. 1939-1940. CC' s-routine. (Box 7, Folder 85)
- Lebedeff, G. A. Rio Piedras, Fv R. 1940-1944 (Box 7, Folder 86)
- Leighty, C. E. 1909-1945 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- Lesley, J. W. 1914-1924 (Box 7, Folder 88)
- Lewis, R. D. Columbus, Ohio 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Love, H. B. 1926-1927 (Box 7, Folder 90)
- Love, J. J. 1914-1939 (Box 7, Folder 91)
- McGraw-Hill Book Co., N. Y. C. 1935 (Box 7, Folder 92)
- MacMillan Company 1911 (Box 7, Folder 93)
- Correspondence -M- 1924-1931 (Box 7, Folder 94)
- Mailing List N. D. (Box 7, Folder 95)
- Mann, A. R. 1909-1922 (Box 7, Folder 96)
- Mann, A. R. 1923-1946 (Box 7, Folder 97)
- Mann, F. T. 1910 (Box 7, Folder 98)
- Memoranda of Understanding, Correspondence, M. A. Carleton 1912-1915 (Box 7, Folder 99)
- Middleton, G. K. 1926-1929 (Box 7, Folder 100)
- Moe, G. G. 1928-1929 (Box 7, Folder 101)
- Myers, C. E. State College, Pa. 1948 (Box 7, Folder 102)
- Myers, C. H. 1905-1909 (Box 7, Folder 103)
- Myers, C. H. 1910 (Box 7, Folder 104)
- Myers, C. H. 1913-1936 (Box 7, Folder 105)
- Myers. C. H. 1940-1944 & N. D. (Box 7, Folder 106)
- Myers, Dean W. I. 1943-1949 (Box 7, Folder 107)
- Correspondence -W- 1942-1948 - (Box 7, Folder 108)
- Newman, J. T. 1910-1928 Property in Cayuga Hts. (Box 7, Folder 109)
- Nolla, J. A. B. P. R. 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 110)
- Nolla, J. A. B. P. R. 1941-1947 (Box 7, Folder 111)
- Nolla, J. A. B. P. R. (manuscript) N. D. (Box 7, Folder 112)
- Correspondence -P- 1949 (Box 7, Folder 113)
- Parker, J. H. 1926-1948 (Box 7, Folder 114)
- Paterson, D. D. 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 115)
- Pearl, Raymond 1910-1915 (Box 7, Folder 116)
- Correspondence re: Dr. Love's original appointment to Thailand, 1949-1950. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Correspondence re: Dr. Love's second year in the Far East, 1951-1952. (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Material re: OFAR' s authorization of the new position, 1950-1953. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Material re: passports, foreign fund exchange and itinerary, 1948-1950. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- USDA and OFAR travel authorization and freight statement, 1949-1950. (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Expense accounts and allowances, 1949-1950. (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Expense accounts and allowances, 1951. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Expense accounts and allowances, 1952. (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Correspondence re: Foreign Operations Administration and rate of pay, 1954-1955 and K. D. (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Correspondence re: drivers for Dr. Love in Thailand, 1951-1953. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Correspondence between H. H. Love and his secretary (Frances Feehan), 1950. " (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Correspondence between H. H. Love and his secretary (Frances Feehan), 1951. " (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Correspondence between H. H. Love and his secretary (Frances Feehan), 1952-1953. (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Bank Statements, and receipts, 1950-1954. (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Cancelled checks, 1950-1954. (Box 8, Folder l5.)
- Insurance, 1950-1955. (Box 8, Folder 16)
- The Rotary Club, 1956. (Box 8, Folder 17)
- General correspondence during K. H. Love's stay in Thailand, 1951-1953. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 4 pp. typescript from R. W. Wiggans, mainly news of Plant Breeding Department., Feb. 7, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - From "Dick" (J. R. King), St. Croix, Virgin Islands, concerning controversy between the Office of Experiment Stations and the AAAS re: the proposed publication of an article in the May 22, 1953 issue of Science., May 10, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Has just moved to Horticultural Research Center, Louisiana State Univ., Baton Rouge. Letters make references to dissatisfaction with Mutual Security Administration., June 6, 28, July 30, Nov. 1, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 6 pp. handwritten letter from Sanford Atwood reporting Cornell Plant Breeding Department news., Aug. 4, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - From "Larry," Singapore, re: arrival of General William ("Wild Bill") Donovan as ambassador to Thailand., Aug. 31, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - P. W. Tsou, encl. cc of letter to W. I. Myers re: possible employment opportunities with international organizations; also letter of Dec. 15th., Oct. 13, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - John L. Mott, NYC. [not John R. Mott], Nov. 13, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - From "Knowles" (Knowles A. Ryerson), Taipeh; also from American Embassy, Manila, P. I., Nov. 26th., Nov. 4, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Also from "Larry", Bakersfield, California, further on M. S. A., Donovan in Thailand; references to R. L. Pendleton of Johns Hopkins., Nov. 14, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - From Robert L. Pendleton; also, carbons of letters to "Dick" (King?) from R. L. P. and social correspondence of Mrs. Pendleton. (Ref. to Donovan in Dec. 6 letter.), Nov. 17, 21, Dec. 6, 15, 20, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- General correspondence during H. H. Love's stay in Thailand, Jan.-Mar., 1954. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Royse P. Murphy, Plant Breeding Department news., Jan. 3, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - From Pendleton in Baltimore. (Feb. 18 letter is cc to Dick, Feb. 19 contains ref. to Knowles.), Jan. 8, 21, Feb. 18, 19, also Mar. 1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - From Knowles A. Ryerson, Dean of College of Agriculture, Berkeley., Feb. 15, Mar. 23, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Cc of letter from Raymond D. Meade, Director of the A. U. A. Language Center in Bangkok, sending credentials of a Thai police corporal to Michigan State; wishes to study police administration and is being sponsored by the Criminal Investigation Division of the Thai National Police. Also visa request document for student, Mar. 5th., Feb. 27, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Further correspondence of R. L. King, at L. S. U., more on F. O. A., - also, carbon copies of letters from HHL at Bangkok to various colleagues concerning positions available in his field., Jan.-Mar. 1954, passim (Box 8, Folder 19)
- General correspondence during H. H. Love's stay in Thailand, Apr.-July, 1954. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Letters from Bill Pan, formerly at Cairo, Erwin R. Brooks, Donald C. Kerr (re: Thai police corporal mentioned in Feb. 27, 1954 letter from Meade in Folder 19), Pendleton, King, and others. Also, carbons of HHL ' s letters to Ryerson and other colleagues; and cc's of Pendleton 's letters to third parties., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- General correspondence during H. K. Love's stay in Thailand, Aug.-Nov. 1954. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Including letters from Kerr, Pendleton, King; also one letter from Horace W. Ryburn, Sept. 24th, on Presbyterian mission work in Thailand., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- General correspondence during H. H. Love's stay in Thailand, Dec. 1954-1955. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - From Pendleton and others; also CU faculty Christmas letters., 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- General correspondence during H. H. Love's stay in Thailand, N. D. (incl. letters from "Dick" (King). (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Correspondence between the Loves and their offspring, 1951-1953. (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Carbons of letters re: men for the Thailand Project, 1951-1952. (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Memorandums on needs and requirements of the technical and economic assistance program in Thailand, 1950 and N. D. (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Reports and notes on Thailand and its agriculture, 1956-1957 and N. D. (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Rice Improvement plans, 1944, 1950, and N. D. (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Tables on the rice yields of various localities of Thailand, 1951-1954. (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Confidential - Country Study on Thailand, 1950. (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Pendleton report on Thailand, 1949. (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Studies of Thailand's soil, crops, and geography, 1929, 1936, and N. D. (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Reports to the Director -General of the Thai Dept. of Agriculture, 1951. (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Quarterly reports of the OFAR mission to Thailand, 1950. (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Periodic reports, newsletters and suggestions, 1950-1952 and N. D. (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Correspondence with Khun Luang re: memorandum on Thailand's rice program, 1950-1951. (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Two papers re: agricultural progress; the church and the Point Four Program, N. D. (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Basic information on Burma and Thailand, N. D. (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Correspondence re: men for agricultural officer's position, at Bangkok, 1954. (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Correspondence with R. E. Moore re: the training of Agricultural Experts, etc., 1946-1954. (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Fertilizer research by Edwards in Chiengmai, Thailand, 1950-1951. (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Correspondence re: Cornell, Taiwan, Thailand, 1951-1953. (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Restricted - manuscript of C. W. Chang's trip to Ceylon, 1951- (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Brief information on the Forestry situation in Thailand, N. D. (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Restricted - A preliminary report on the Cha-Cherng-Sao Pilot Project, 1951. (Box 8, Folder 45)
- The community development program in India, 1955. (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Rice information compiled by the research division of the Bank of Thailand, 1937-1950. (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Recommendations re: priorities in technical and economic program, 1950 and N. D. (Box 8, Folder 48)
- F. J. Rossiter of the Office of Foreign Agricultural Relations, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Correspondence re: rumor of Pencileton's removal from Thailand, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Photographs of H. H. Love in Thailand N. B. (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Typed copy of pp. 1-82 of "The Nanking Story" N. D. (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Material re: The Nanking Project, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Plant Breeding 103: outline and tables of variation, 1915-1921 & N. D. (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Book of regulations for Thai Government students (written in Thai and English) N. D. (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Copy of the "Standard" ' weekly international newspaper- July 8, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Copy of the "Standard" ' weekly international newspaper- Mar. 15, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Copy of the "Standard" ' weekly international newspaper- Aug. 2, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Copy of the "Standard" ' weekly international newspaper- Feb. 21, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Copy of the "Standard" ' weekly international newspaper- Feb. 28, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Miscellaneous tables, notes and typed parts of a manuscript N. D. (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Miscellaneous tables, notes, and typed parts of a manuscript N. D (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Tables for a report on the rice tests N. D. (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Tables for a report on the rice tests N. D. (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Tables for a report on the rice tests N. D. (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Photographs used for the Siam Society Talk by H. H. Love N. D. (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Photographs of Thai and Indonesian Rice Stations N. D. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Photographs of Thai and Indonesian Rice Stations N. D. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Album of Photographs: Dr. Love's Rice Book N. D. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Photographs of Thai Rice Stations and surrounding areas of interest N. D. (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Photographs of workmen applying fertilizer to the soil ' Dr. Love: EGA N. D. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Photographs of the Thai Rice Station Team N. D. (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Booklet on the International Church N. D. (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Love's answers to USIS Radio Section Questions N. D. (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Resolution re: the retirement of H. H. Love, 1949. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Article: "Is Agricultural Research Important?" N. D. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Correspondence re: job description, supplies and hybrid corn in Thailand, 1950. (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Rough copy of a report to the Director of Agriculture, 1950. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Retirement letters, articles and resolutions from the University, 1949. (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Photographs of Japanese rice culture N. D. (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Report on Thailand's rice improvement investigations, 1955-1956. (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Report on the progress of the University of the Philippines College of Agriculture following the termination of the Cornell contract N. E. (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Disorganized manuscript on the struggles of a Chinese farm boy N. D. (Box 9, Folder 18)
- A preliminary report on the idea of using Italian methods for Thai rice production N. D. (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Research report on Industrial utilization of rice-by-products in Thailand N. D. (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Planning for a survey of nutritional deficiencies in tropical livestock, 1952. (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Rotary dinner report (Bangkok), 1953. (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Confidential letters re: Love's and Pendleton's salary and retirement from STEM, also re: The Thai View of the U. S., 1951-1954. (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Dr. Love - recent correspondence, 1949-1958 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Rotary International four-way test, 1954 & N. D. (Box 9, Folder 25)
- "Loy Krathong" by Senator Phya Anuman Rajdhon, 1950. (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Correspondence re: Griffin Mission, etc. 1950 & N. D. (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Statistic tables N. D. (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Booklets and reports re: statistics, 1949-1950. (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Australian agricultural journal, 1951. (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Agricultural journal of Ceylon, 1951. (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Rotary international ' Bangkok and Ceylon, 1946-1955. (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Thailand ' natural resources, income, etc., 1949-1953. (Box 9, Folder 33)
- American publications on foreign agriculture, 1950. (Box 9, Folder 34)
- United Nations Bulletin, 1949. (Box 9, Folder 35)
- U. S. information service bulletin, 1951. (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Thai publications N. D. (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous articles, etc. including a notebook. 1952-1955 & N. D. (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Journals of the Siam Society, 1951. (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Journals of the Siam Society, 1952. (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Journals of the Siam Society, 1953. (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Journals of the Siam Society, 1954. (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Journals of the Siam Society, 1955. (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Journals of the Siam Society, 1956. (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Pamphlets re: Indonesia, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Pamphlets re: Indonesia N. D. (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Taiwan Agricultural Yearbook, 1952. (Box 9, Folder 47)
- The Siam Society- 50th Anniversary commemoration publication- vol. 1. 1954. (Box 9, Folder 48)
- The Siam Society- 50th Anniversary commemoration publication- vol. 2. 1954. (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Book - Indonesia, 1951. (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Articles and papers - H. H. Love rice program - Thailand - 1952 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Articles and papers - H. H. Love rice program - Thailand - 1953 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Articles and papers - H. H. Love rice program - Thailand - 1954 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Articles and papers - H. H. Love rice program - Thailand - 1955 and n. d. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Ithaca-Cornell Oat Data (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Articles and papers by Love on Gen. Plant Breeding, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Statements re: the rice program, 1951-1953 and n. d. (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Material used for statement on rice production, 1942-1951 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Material used for statement on rice production, 1952-1955 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Material used for statement on rice production, n. d. (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Report on Thailand land development, n. d. (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Photographs used for rice production statement, n. d. (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Letters, 1944-1950 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Clippings and other things, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Clippings and other things, 1952-1955 and n. d. (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Tables for method study report, 1939-1953 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Statistics-tables, etc., n. d. (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Statistics - extracts from paper by John Wishart, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Statistics - extracts from paper by Yates, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Statistics - the calculation of the Dosage-Mortality Curve, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Statistics - tables for Mendelian Ratio of "C" - n. d. (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Pamphlets on oats and maize, 1950-1951 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Papers of 1952 rice meeting (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Transformations and Interactions, 1941-1948 and n. d. (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Outline for rice improvement seminar talk; Is Research Important? n. d. (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Rice clippings and related material, 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Rice clippings and related material, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Rice clippings and related material, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Rice clippings and related material, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Rice clippings and related material, n. d. (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Some notes on the importance of Agricultural research for Thailand by Pendleton, 1940. (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Agricultural production targets of Taiwan, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Japanese rice methods applied to India and Thailand, 1953-1954. (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Land and crops of Thailand and Malaya, 1943-1953 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Pamphlets on rice, 1915-1953 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Statistical and mathematical material, 1927-1952 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Papers re: international rice commission of United Nations, etc., 1954-1955 and n. d. (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Correspondence from K. G. Gairdner to Love and Pendleton, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Book re: Japan's ecological crop geography, etc., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- R. L. Pendleton, Manila, Philippines, 1934-1936 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- R. L. Pendleton, Manila, Philippines, 1937-1939 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- R. L. Pendleton, Manila, Philippines, 1940-1946 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- V. A. Pesola, 1929-1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- R. H. Porter, 1926-1944 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- R. Purnariksha, Siam, 1937-1940 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Recommendations for Positions, 1909-1924 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Retirement material, 1930-1945 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Retirement information, 1929-1948 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Retirement system, 1929-1949 and n. d. (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Director Arturo Roque, Rio Piedras, Puerto Rico, 1943-1947 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Correspondence - S, 1939-1949 and n. d. (Box 11, Folder 12)
- G. H. Shull, 1909-1923 and n. d. (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Sigma Xi, 1918-1945 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- L. H. Smith, 1909-1920 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Geo. W. Snedecor, Ames, Iowa, 1934-1936 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Synapsis, 1934-1949 and n. d. (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Correspondence - T, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Union Central Life Insurance Co., 1925-1935 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Correspondence -W, 1922-1949 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- C. M. Warren, 1916-1947 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Waverly Press, Baltimore, Md., 1943 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Dr. H. J. Webber, 1919-1946 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- David Weeks re: Bolivia, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- R. G. Wiggans, 1927-1944. See also Box 1, Folders 6-7 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  Includes letter, Apr. 29, 1927, from Wiggans, concerning the assault on Nanking by the Revolutionary Army and the killing of Dr. [John Elias] Williams: "We were totally unprepared for the brutal assault that was made on all foreigners in Nanking and for the utter destruction which they wreaked on all personal property."
- G. J. Wilds, 1923-1950 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- John Wishart, 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Dr. R. S. Woodward, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- M. Yasuda, 1929-1939 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- F. Yates, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Dr. B. Youngblood, Office of Experiment Stations, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Page proof pp. 1-110, for Dr. Love's book on Experimental Methods, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Page proof pp. 111-182, for Dr. Love's book on Experimental Methods, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Page proof pp. 183-229, for Dr. Love's book on Experimental Methods, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Third carbon of ms. for the Exp. Methods Book, pp. 1-70 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Third carbon of ms. for the Exp. Methods Book, pp. 71-140 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Third carbon of ms. for the Exp. Methods Book, pp. 141-210 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Third carbon of ms. for the Exp. Methods Book, pp. 211-280 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Third carbon of ms. for the Exp. Methods Book, pp. 281-354 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Text - For Puerto Rico, original calculations - n. d. (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Text - For Puerto Rico, original calculations - n. d. (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Text - For Puerto Rico, original calculations - n. d. (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Lattice Design 6x6 - typescript copy and corrected carbon, n. d. (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Text - for Puerto Rico - original manuscript I, II, III, n. d. (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Text - for Puerto Rico - original manuscript I, II, III, n. d. (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Text - for Puerto Rico - original manuscript I, II, III, n. d. (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Text- for Puerto Rico - original manuscript IV, n. d. (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Text - for Puerto Rico - original manuscript IV, n. d. (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Text - for Puerto Rico - original manuscript V, reference, n. d. (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Text - for Puerto Rico - original manuscript V, reference, n. d. (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Galley Proof for Experimental Methods Book (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Job letters and carbons, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Job letters and carbons, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- First letters re: rice men salary scale, 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Correspondence re: Kopf, Finkner, and Middleton for Thai Rice Program, 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Correspondence between J. G. Harrar and H. H. Love, 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Agricultural articles by C. W. Chang, n. d. (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Typed copy of rice investigation report, pp. 1-67, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Typed copy of rice investigation report, pp. 74-end, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous materials associated with rice report, 1956 and n. d. (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Statistics and Biometry, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Notes for lecture for Siam Society, n. d. (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Ramiah's notes for Analysis, n. d. (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Reports of OFAR Mission to Thailand, etc., 1950-1955 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Pamphlets on rice; varieties, breeding, etc., 1929-1950 and n. d. (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Pamphlets and magazines re: conditions relating to agriculture, 1930-1952 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Papers re: salary and agricultural notes, 1942-1953 and n. d. (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Thai publication (written in Thai) n. d. (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Book written in German - Erblichkeit in Populationen und in reinen Linien, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Report on Thailand to aid personnel working with U. S. Program of technical cooperation, n. d. (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Directories of government personnel, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Final report of Agricultural Officer - Carl W. Leveau, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Bulletins of the Taiwan Agricultural Research Institute, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Report on Soil Fertility Program by J. S. Owens, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Philippine Rice seed program, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- "The Life of the Farmer" by Phya Amman Rachathon, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Agricultural programs, etc., in China and Japan, 1954 and n. d. (Box 12, Folder 26)
- The Rural Community Development movement in Asia and the Far East, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 27)